CAMERON WARBURTON D.O.B 17/12/1997

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am an ambitious and dedicated individual with a real desire to pursue a long and progressive career within IT. I believe that my attention to detail and my passion and hard work are well suited to a career in IT. I have always had an interest and a passion for IT and I designed my education around this, having chosen GCSE options to enable me to have a career in IT, I followed this up by attending Coleg Cambria for two years and gained my BTEC Level 3 in IT. I have already gained experience in two IT roles and gained 6+ years of experience. I am currently looking for work back in the UK as I am returning in December 2023 after being in Australia and working as a IT Support Officer for Coral Homes. Currently studying to become a Frontend Developer and half way through the course. Please see below links to my Github and E-Portfolio:

Github - https://github.com/CameronWarburton

E-Portfolio - https://cameronwarburton.github.io/Advance-E-Portfolio/

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- IT I have developed these through secondary education as well as through my work experience working with computers and in IT based working environments such as my current position where I have attended courses to further develop my skills.
- Good at working as a team I have worked in Primark and
 McDonalds as part of a team but have gained much wider experience of working within a team in my current role.
- Good communication and good customer service which have been developed even further in my current role.
- Knowledge of business infrastructure I did business studies in school and have worked within various businesses and in different working environments and proven my ability to add value to any business that I work within.
- Problem solving Due to work experience I have developed my problem solving skills through working in a team to meet deadlines and completing tasks as well as individual completion of tasks and deadlines.
- Coding Languages HTML5, CSS, JavaScript. Currently learning REACT.

EXPERIENCE

Work Experience

Coral Homes - IT Support Officer (April 2023 - Present 2023)

I have been working for Coral Homes since April 2023 as an IT Support Officer. My duties in this role have been to create new starter accounts, set up PC's, Laptop's and Phones for new users and be 2nd point of call for any IT support tickets that come through. I am also there to assist the Senior IT Project Coordinator with project work that is being carried out. I also work closely with the first line team to assist with any queries and share my knowledge from my previous IT role.

Redrow - Junior IT Helpdesk Assistant / Junior IT Technician (Oct 2017 – Feb 2023)

I started with Redrow Homes in the role of Junior IT Helpdesk Assistant in October 2017 and progressed to the role of Junior IT Support Technician during this time I have gained experience in an IT working environment and learned and expanded my knowledge within IT. I have attended customer service, time management and challenge and response training courses as well as on the job training. In my current role I am responsible for managing my own workload as well as juggling laptop builds & imaging, website requests, networking work and any regional office visits. I have received the number one award for most calls resolved on a number of occasions and take great pride in winning this monthly award. In the Redrow IT department I use/am familiar with:

- Active Directory (Creating Accounts, System Access, AD Groups)
- Microsoft Office 365
- Redrow in house applications (Overheads System, IT Admin, SBMS Sales etc.)
- MDM Systems
- AutoCAD
- Remote Control Programs (LogMeIn, CMRC)
- RDS (Remote Desktop Server)
- Forticlient (VPN)
- Avaya Workplace and Avaya Phone System
- Sophos Email Appliance
- Sophos Web Appliance
- Sophos Anti-Virus
- Bighand installation
- Azure installation
- VMware
- Netapp
- GFI Events Manager
- Sostenuto (Call Logging System)

MoneySupermarket.com (Work Experience 2016)

During my BTEC Level 3 IT course I was the only student offered an opportunity at money supermarket.com. Although I was only there for one week the experience I gained was invaluable and gave me my first real taste of working in an IT environment and as part of a team.

West Cheshire College – Admin Assistant (Ellesmere Port Campus (Oct 2016 – April 2017)

Having completed and passed my IT Level 3 I started to look for my first career step in the IT sector. This was presented to me when I successfully applied for a job at the West Cheshire College. The role was a temporary one due to government funding but I continued to be offered extensions until the funding ran out in April 2017. I enjoyed working for West Cheshire College and it gave me my first time experience in a full-time position. I worked in the M.I.S. department and my main duties were to update registers, create spreadsheets displaying requested information from the system, printing timetables, enrolling students, room bookings and filing files. Working here allowed me to experience what working in a full-time role was like and enabled me to use the IT Skills I had acquired at college.

Blue Machinery Spares limited - Data Analyst (April 2017 – October 2017)

On an Ad Hoc basis I have covered the role of Data Analyst at Blue Spares, this in essence was maternity cover but it allowed me to gain multiple experiences in a fast moving successful business. During my time here I worked on the business IT system and exported data out of the system for further analysis. I produced reports for the Sales Director and this involved creating pivot tables, producing graphical presentations and analyzing customer spends by product groups. I also produced costings and set up Macros to enable faster processing of data. I also liaised with the Group IT Manager and set up a number of new employee computers installing all relevant software and ensuring all network connections were in place. Although this role was on an adhoc basis I gained real experience in an IT role.

EDUCATION	.1	ıN	\cap	П	١٦	٠,		ш		-
	V	ш	U	ш	١.	. -	·	U	U	_

Subject	Grade
BTEC Science	Pass
IT	В
Business	С
PE short course	D
Product Design	С
RS	С
English	С

Math's C

IT Core Pass

Welsh D

Welsh BAC Pass

Level 3 ICT BTEC DIPLOMA MMP (Merit Merit Pass)

Frontend Developer Course – Midway through the course and still learning each day. Studied HTML 5, CSS and JavaScript so far and will be moving on to REACT next. Github and E-Portfolio linked above. Hoping to receive my certificate for this course by the end of the year.

LEADERSHIP

D of E (Duke of Edinburgh) I did my volunteering in a primary school. I helped them develop their rounder's skills and participate in games. I entered the bronze award which I got awarded at Castle Alun High School. D of E helped me develop some skills such as map reading, setting up tents, leadership and cooking skills. I had to carry food and drink and part of the tent for my group. I was expected to cook my own dinner and put up my tent as part of group. I was trustworthy and reliable throughout. I also had to use negotiation skills to stop arguments in my group.

REFERENCES

Available on request